raketherake.com 2017-12-13

# Rakeback - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.

  1. The Armchair Partners Ltd Group of companies is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you.
  2. When registering with our site and for our newsletter, we use your personal information to update you about our news and services. We will only contact you with your consent and you can unsubscribe from our emails newsletters at any time in you account or by clicking unsubscribe from within any email.
  3. We do not sell, rent or exchange your personal information with any third party for commercial reasons.
  4. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access in accordance with the UK data protection legislation.
  5. We do not collect sensitive information about you except when you specifically knowingly provide it. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details by contacting us.
  6. If you have any questions about our privacy statement please contact us.

## Cookies

Websites use cookies. A cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer's hard drive. This site uses cookies to improve your visitor experience and search possibilities. If you are registered with our site, the cookie will also manage your login and session on the members only parts of the site.

If you do not want your computer to receive and store cookies, you can alter your security settings within your web browser (Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Safari etc). However, please note that certain parts of our site may only be used fully if your browser allows cookies.

**By disabling cookies you may find your experience of our site is restricted.**

### 1) Our Cookies

We can categorise the cookies we use into two types, essential cookies and performance cookies. The tables below detail the cookies we use and what their purpose is.

#### Essential Cookies

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to use the website and/or use its features such as accessing secure areas. Without these cookies parts of the site will not function correctly.

Cookie name | Description | Expires After  
---|---|---  
ASP.NET_SessionId | This is a temporary session cookie that is set whenever you visit the site and is used to record a session/visit to the website. The contents of these cookies is unique ID number. Without this cookie you will not be able to login or register. | End of session  
RakeTheRakeAuth | This cookie is used for security, to identify you to the site once you have logged on so that the site can grant you access to the members-only areas of the site and show you your own personal account content. | End of session  
RakeTheRakeAuthMark | For security reasons, the main security cookie (RakeTheRakeAuth) is only transmitted over a secure connection (HTTPS). This cookie indicates to the site that you are logged on even when you are not using a secure connection, so that the site may move you back onto a secure connection in order to 'see' you as logged on in order to provide you with your relevant account content. | 30 minutes  
bb_sessionhash | Cookies with the prefix bb_ and bbb_ are used by the forum software (vBulletin) that we have built into the site here www.raketherake.com/rakeback-forum. This vBulletin cookie is needed for maintaining session state and security. It's checked on every page load. | End of session  
bb_lastvisit | This vBulletin cookie updates the last visit and last activity times for guests and registered users. Last visit is set to the last activity time (before it's updated). Last activity is always set to the specified time. | 1 year  
bb_lastactivity | This vBulletin cookie checks what you did when you last used the Site. This is a constantly updated cookie. | 1 year  
w3tc_referrer | This W3 Total Cache cookie is used as part of our caching (speed optimisation) on the WordPress blog section of our site. | End of session  
Stats_NextUpdate_2 | This cookie is part of the secure SSO (Single Sign On) mechanism between the RakeTheRake and DragTheBar site.  It helps maintain a logon session on the DragTheBar site so that when you follow a link within the RakeTheRake site to the DragTheBar site you do not need to login separately in order to access that link. | 5 minutes  
Stats_Complete | is also part of the SSO mechanism between the RakeTheRake and DragTheBar site.  It helps ensure you are logged out of the DragTheBar site as soon as you log out of the RakeTheRake site, for security reasons. | End of session  
  
#### Essential Cookies (DragTheBar)

Creating an account with RakeTheRake automatically creates an account with our partner site DragTheBar.com. A number of the cookies below are required to keep both accounts synchronised securely.

Cookie name | Description | Expires After  
---|---|---  
uk | This is a temporary session cookie that is set after login only. The content of these cookies is for third-parties interoperability. It contains login information for keeping tracking between pages. | End of session  
_ujlkk | This is also a temporary session cookie that is set after login only. The contents of these cookies is the username you entered for login. This helps us pre-fill login forms as well some third-parties interoperability. | End of session  
SessionID  
(dragthebar.com) | This is a temporary session ID created as part of the DragTheBar account synchronisation. Without this cookie you will not be able to login or register. | End of session  
bbb_sessionhash  
(dragthebar.com) | This DragTheBar vBulletin cookie is needed for maintaining session state and security. It's checked on every page load. | End of session  
bbb_lastvisit  
(dragthebar.com) | This DragTheBar vBulletin cookie updates the last visit and last activity times for guests and registered users. Last visit is set to the last activity time (before it's updated). Last activity is always set to the specified time. | 1 year  
bbb_lastactivity  
(dragthebar.com) | This DragTheBar vBulletin cookie checks what you did when you last used the Site. This is a constantly updated cookie. | 1 year  
  
#### Performance Cookies

Performance Cookies collect information about how you interact with the site. These cookies do not collect any information that identifies you personally and they are only used to improve the performance of our website.

Google Analytics is a widely used service by site owners and webmasters to gather statistics about how visiors interact with the website. These statistics are used to help us make improvements to the site. For more information about Google Analytics and their cookies [click here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies "Google Analytics Cookies").

Cookie name | Description | Expires After  
---|---|---  
RakeTheRake.User.Visited | This cookies improves usability and lets us know if it's you first visit to the website. If it is your first visit,we show an initial introduction to our services and if not we show the standard content. | 1 month  
HideRakebackOffers | This cookie simply remembers your preference for showing/hiding the offers drop down menu. | 29 years  
_utma | This Google Analytics cookie keeps track of the number of times a visitor has been to the site, when their first visit was, and when their last visit occurred. | 2 years  
_utmb | Holds timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor first visits the site | 30 minutes  
_utmc | Holds timestamp of the exact moment in time when a visitor leaves the site | End of session  
__utmz | Keeps track of where the visitor came from, what search engine they used, what link was clicked on, what keyword they used, and where in the world they are when they accessed the website. | 6 months  
  
### 2) Third Party Cookies

Cookies are also set by third parties on this site. More information about cookies placed by third parties and how to restrict or block their cookies can be accessed by following the link to their website below.

Name | Description | Restricting these Cookies  
---|---|---  
Facebook | The facebook cookies are used to let Facebook know you are logged in to Facebook and to help you use social share buttons. | [more information](http://www.facebook.com/help/?page=176591669064814)  
Google Analytics | These cookies collect statistics on visitors to the site, where vistors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. This helps us to understand how people use the site and to make improvements to our site. | [more information](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)  
Twitter.com | Twitter use cookies to better understand how you interact with their services when logged in. They are also used in the functionality of the social sharing buttons. | [more information](http://twitter.com/privacy)  
Flickr (Yahoo) | These cookies are created as a result of the Flickr photo feed used on our blog pages. | [ more information](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/uk/yahoo/?pir=ZyCPK55ibUkRRNJkkp.Wrcjv.O7tvpJr1FEa0vCr2RI1gE_m9fDn2xfqlqD5MvA-#4)  
  
If you have any further questions about the cookies we use on the site please feel free to contact us.
